September 11, 2001 Documentary Project Collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- SERIES I: MANUSCRIPT MATERIALS (Box 1-12)
  - Clippings and Online Articles
    - The Orion (California State University, Chico). Sent in by Juan Valdes., 85 pages (Box 12, Folder 110)
      (See Reports subseries in Manuscripts).
    - Paradise Post (Chico, California) (folder 1 of 2). Sent in by Karen Brown of California State University, Chico students., 55 pages (Box 12, Folder 111)
      (See Reports subseries in Manuscripts) (See oversize Box 38 for original newspaper print)
    - Paradise Post (Chico, California) (folder 2 of 2); sent in by Karen Brown of California State University, Chico students., 110 pages (Box 12, Folder 112)
      (See Reports subseries in Manuscripts).(See oversize Box 38 for original newspaper print).
- SERIES II: SOUND RECORDINGS (Box 13-34, 41)
  - Audiocassettes
    - SR001, SR004-009, SR015-022, SR024-027 (Box 13)
    - SR028-045 (Box 14)
    - SR046-063 (Box 15)
    - SR064-071, SR073-080, SR082-085 (Box 16)
    - SR086-088, SR090-105 (Box 17)
    - SR106-123 (Box 18)
    - SR124-140 (Box 19)
    - SR141-144, SR146-159 (Box 20)
    - SR160-177 (Box 21)
    - SR178-194 (Box 22)
    - SR195-200, SR202-203, SR205, SR207-215 (Box 23)
    - SR216-229, SR231-233 (Box 24)
    - SR234, SR239, SR242, SR245-259 (Box 25)
    - SR260-277 (Box 26)
    - SR278-296 (Box 27)
    - SR297-314 (Box 28)
    - SR315-322, SR326, SR328-336 (Box 29)
    - SR337-355 (Box 30)
    - SR356-372, SR375 (Box 31)
    - SR376-379, SR381-386 (Box 32)
  - Digital Audio Tape
    - SR206 (Box 33)
  - Mini-audiocassettes
    - SR003, SR072, SR089, SR230, SR236-238, SR240-241, SR243-244, SR380 (Box 33)
  - Compact Discs
    - SR002, SR010-014, SR023, SR069, SR081, SR089, SR145, SR193, SR204, SR235, SR323-325, SR373 (Box 34)
  - Zip Disc
    - SR327 (also CF12) (Box *41)
      *Disc is a digital sound recording
- SERIES III: GRAPHIC IMAGES (Box 35-38, 48)
  - Contact sheets (PH001-005) (Box 35, Folder 113)
    See also: Negatives (PH006-037)
  - Black-and-white negatives (PH006-037) (Box 35, Folder 114)
    See also: Contact sheets (PH001-005)
  - Black-and-white photographs (PH038-042) (Box 35, Folder 115)
  - Digital photographic prints (PH043-051) (Box 35, Folder 116)
  - Color photographs (PH052-063, PH336-343) (Box 35, Folder 117)
  - Color slides (PH064-083) (Box 36, Folder 118)
  - Color slides (PH084-100) (Box 36, Folder 119)
  - Color slides (PH101-120) (Box 36, Folder 120)
  - Color slides (PH121-134) (Box 36, Folder 121)
  - Color slides (PH135-154) (Box 36, Folder 122)
  - Color slides (PH155-174) (Box 36, Folder 123)
  - Color slides (PH175-194) (Box 36, Folder 124)
  - Color slides (PH195-200) (Box 36, Folder 125)
  - Digital Images (PH201-343) (Box 36, Folder 126)
    See Electronic Media: Folder 142 (PH201-282), Folder 133 (PH283-334), Box 37 (PH335/GR01), Folder 117 (PH336-343), Folder 144 (PH402)
  - Black-and-white photographs (PH344-363) (Box 36, Folder 127)
    See Box 48 See also Contact sheets: (PH364-368; PH371; PH373-376; PH382; PH384; PH392-393; PH396-398)
  - Contact sheets (PH364-PH401) (Box 36, Folder 128)
    See also Photographs (PH344-363)
  - Digital photographic prints (PH403-PH404) (Box 36, Folder 129)
    See Box 48 See also Contact sheet: (PH005)
  - Graphic materials (GR01-15) (Box 37)
  - Graphic materials (GR16-19) (Box 38 (oversize))
    (See map folder in Reading Room for GR16)
  - PH344-363, PH403-404 (Box 48 (oversize))
- SERIES IV: MOVING IMAGES (Box 39-40)
  - MV01, MV04 (copy 2), MV05 (copy 2), MV06-10 (Box 39)
  - MV02, MV03, MV04 (copy 1), MV05 (copy 1), MV11-18 (Box 40)
- SERIES V: ELECTRONIC MEDIA (Box 41, 1)
  - Electronic media (CF01) (Box 41, Folder 130)
  - Electronic media (CF02) (Box 41, Folder 131)
  - Electronic media (CF03/SR323) (Box 41, Folder 132)
  - Electronic media (CF04/PH283-291) (Box 41, Folder 133)
  - Electronic media (CF05/PH292-299) (Box 41, Folder 134)
  - Electronic media (CF06/PH300-308) (Box 41, Folder 135)
  - Electronic media (CF07/PH309-317) (Box 41, Folder 136)
  - Electronic media (CF08/PH318-326) (Box 41, Folder 137)
  - Electronic media (CF09/PH327-334) (Box 41, Folder 138)
  - Electronic media (CF10) (Box 41, Folder 139)
  - Electronic media (CF11) (Box 41, Folder 140)
  - Electronic media (CF12/SR327) (Box 41, Folder 141)
  - Electronic media (CF13/PH201-282) (Box 41, Folder 142)
  - Electronic media (CF14) (Box 41, Folder 143)
    See Box 1
  - Electronic media (CF15/PH402) (Folder 144)
- SERIES VI: ARTIFACTS (Box 42-47)
  - AR01-04 (Box 42)
    Bumper stickers
  - AR05
    Scrapbook from Children International- Chile
  - AR06 (Box 43)
    Scrapbook from Children International-Asia
  - AR07 (Box 44)
    Book of condolences from Hillside Funeral Home, Kansas
  - AR08-13, AR16 (Box 45)
    Engraved copper plates that were taken to the memorial site. Donated by the Knoxville Writers' Guild, Tennessee
  - AR14
    Plastic flag donated by the Knoxville Writers' Guild, Tennessee (See oversize Box 38).
  - AR15
    Small card
  - AR17
    Poem entitled, "The Aftermath"
  - AR18-19
    Red and blue ribbons
  - AR20
    Poem, "I am persuaded..."
  - AR21
    Newspaper printed in French from Quebec
  - AR22
    Paper advertisement about Osama Bin Laden, "Have you Seen Me?"
  - AR38
    American flag made of sequins (hand made)
  - AR23 (Box 46)
    American flag
  - AR24-AR37 (Box 47)
    Audiocassettes AR24-AR33 and floppy discs AR34-AR37 Note: These are irradiated objects.
Appendix A: Donating Institutions
Alma College
American Folklife Center
American RadioWorks
Appleseed Recordings
Bronx Satellite Academy
California State University, Chico
Center for the Study of Upper Midwestern Cultures
Colorado College
Crestwood High School (Pa.)
Duke University. Center for Documentary Studies
Davenport Public Library (Ia.)
Fairfax Community Adult School (Calif.)
Fort Dodge Public Library (Ia.)
Harvard University
Heritage Christian School (Ia.)
Hiawatha Library (Ia.)
Hunter College
Indiana University
Iowa City Public Library (Ia.)
Iowa. Dept. of Cultural Affairs
Lake Tahoe Community College (Calif.)
Long Beach Historical Society (Calif.)
Montville High School (Conn.)
Naples American High School (Naples, Italy)
National Czech & Slovak Museum & Library
Northwest Iowa Library Service Area
Plymouth State College. Institute for New Hampshire Studies
RipBang Pictures (Md.)
Salt Institute for Documentary Studies
September School (Colo,)
Sidney Public High School (Ia.)
State Historical Society of Iowa
State Library of Iowa
St. Andrews Episcopal Church (Ca.)
Southern Illinois University at Edwardsville
Sumner High School (Me.)
Trinity College of Graduate Studies (Ca.)
University of California, Los Angeles
University of California, San Diego
University of Central Florida
University of Colorado, Boulder
University of Pennsylvania
Utah State University
Valley High School (West Des Moines, Iowa)
Appendix B: Locations Where Recordings were Made
Italy
Naples
United States
Arizona
California
Colorado
Connecticut
District of Columbia
Florida
Georgia
Idaho
Illinois
Indiana
Iowa
Maine
Maryland
Massachusetts
Michigan
Minnesota
Nevada
New Hampshire
New Jersey
New Mexico
New York
North Carolina
Oklahoma
Oregon
Pennsylvania
Pennsylvania
Tennessee
Utah
Virginia
Washington
Wisconsin